{
  "minecraft-version": "نسخهٔ ماین کرفت",
  "plugin-load-problem": "افزونه '{{plugin-name}}' قادر به بارگیری نمی باشد.",
  "pocketmine-version": "نسخه Pocketmine",
  "bedrock-version": "نسخه bedrock",
  "forge-version": "نسخه forge",
  "authme-shutdown-problem": "افزونه 'AuthMe' قادر به اجرا نبوده و سرور را متوقف می کند.",
  "pex-config-problem": "فایل پیکربندی پلاگین 'PermissionsEx' نامعتبر است.",
  "ambiguous-plugin-name-problem": "درحال حاضر چندین فایل برای پلاگین '{{plugin-name}}' وجود دارد: '{{first-plugin-path}}' و '{{second-plugin-path}}'.",
  "plugin-dependency-problem": "پلاگین '{{plugin-name}}' به پلاگین '{{dependency-plugin-name}}' نیاز دارد.",
  "plugin-disabling-problem": "نمیتوان پلاگین '{{plugin-name}}' را غیر فعال کرد.",
  "plugin-enabling-problem": "نمیتوان پلاگین '{{plugin-name}}' را فعال کرد.",
  "plugin-runtime-problem": "این افزونه '{{plugin-name}}' در حال اجرا با مشکلی مواجه شد.",
  "forge-confirm-problem": "فورج به تایید شما نیاز دارد تا تغییرات را ثبت کند و سرور را شروع کند.",
  "mod-dependency-problem": "مود '{{mod-name}}' نیازمند به مود {{dependency-mod-name}} است.",
  "mod-dependency-problem-plural": "مود '{{mod-name}}' نیازمند به مود {{dependency-mod-list}} است.",
  "mod-duplicate-problem": "برای مود '{{mod-name}}' چندین فایل یافت شده است: '{{first-mod-path}}' و '{{second-mod-path}}'.",
  "mod-exception-problem": "مود '{{mod-name}}' یک مشکل ایجاد کرده است.",
  "mod-fatal-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has a fatal error.",
  "world-missing-mod-problem": "The world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' which appears to be missing.",
  "world-mod-version-problem": "This world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' version {{mod-expected-version}} and it is now at version {{mod-current-version}}.",
  "plugin-incompatible-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is incompatible with your current server version.",
  "aquatic-world-on-older-version-problem": "The current world was created/loaded with Minecraft 1.13 or higher. The new format cannot be loaded in any older version.",
  "old-player-directory-problem": "The server has detected an old player directory in the world save.",
  "command-run-solution": "Run the command '{{command}}'.",
  "authme-shutdown-solution": "Set 'stopServer' to 'true'.",
  "configure-plugin": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}}.",
  "configure-plugin-with-file": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}} ({{suggested-file}}).",
  "plugin-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-install-solution": "Install the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-remove-solution": "Remove the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "file-delete-solution": "Delete the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "file-edit-solution": "Edit the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "mod-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution": "مود {{mod-name}} را نصب کنید.",
  "mod-install-solution-with-version": "مود {{mod-name}} با نسخه {{mod-version}} را نصب کنید.",
  "mod-remove-solution": "مود {{mod-name}} را حذف کنید.",
  "aquatic-version-install-solution": "سرور را به نسخه 1.13 یا جدیدتر به روز کنید.",
  "plugin-command-exception-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' cannot execute the command '{{command}}'.",
  "ticking-block-entity-problem": "A block in the world is causing problems.",
  "remove-block-solution": "Remove the block from the world, e.g. with MCEdit.",
  "do-nothing-solution": "Do nothing. This problem might fix itself.",
  "chunk-load-exception-problem": "There was an exception while loading the world chunks.",
  "remove-chunk-solution": "Remove the problematic chunk from the world, e.g. with MCEdit or by removing the region file.",
  "multiverse-load-problem": "The world '{{world-name}}' could not be loaded because it contains errors and is probably corrupt.",
  "world-repair-solution": "Repair the world '{{world-name}}', e.g. by using Minecraft Region Fixer or MCEdit.",
  "world-duplicate-problem": "World '{{world-name}}' is a duplicate of another world and has been prevented from loading.",
  "mod-wrong-minecraft-version-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is not compatible with the Minecraft version {{minecraft-version}}.",
  "forge-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different Forge version."
}